Guide to the Cornell Migrant Program records, [ca. 1953-2005]
Cornell Migrant Program records, [ca. 1953-2005]
- Series XXII. Immigration Policy and Reports
  - Anti Discrimination Training Materials Migration and Development in the Caribbean Basin: Implication and Recommendations for policy - Robert A. Pastor 1989-11 Development and Migration: A Comparative Analysis of two Mexican Migrant Circuits - Luin Goldring, 1990-05 US Immigration Policy: Restoring Credibility/A Report to Congress, 1994 U.S. Immigration Policy: Restoring Credibility, 1994 Legal Immigration: Setting Priorities, 1995 Immigration from Central America: Some Thoughts on It's Causes and Cures Feinberg and Carlisle, 1989-07 Unauthorized Migration: An Economic Development Response, 1990-07 Illegal Aliens, 1986-04 GAO U.S. Mexico Trade, 1991-05 GAO Testimony - Immigration Reform Status of Employer Sanctions, 1989-05 GAO Immigration Reform: Potential Impact on West Coast Farm Labor, 1989-09 GAO Immigration Reform: Status of Implementing Employer Sanctions After Second Year, 1988-11 GAO Immigration Reform: Status of Implementing Employer Sanctions After One Year, 1987-11 Employer Sanctions and U.S. Labor Markets: Second Report, 1991 Immigration Reform: The Effects of Employer Sanctions and Legalizations on Wages, 1991 Impact of IRCA on the U.S. Labor Market and Economy, 1991 International Migration in North America: Issues, Polices, and Implications, 1992 Immigration Reform and Agricultural Labor - Robert Coltrane Research Perspectives on Migration: Immigration, their Families and their Communities in the Aftermath of Welfare Reform Threatened Peoples Threatened Borders: World Migration and U.S. Policy, 1994 Guide to Alien Eligibility for Federal Programs Welfare Reform and the Development of Immigration policy, 1997-08 The Effects of Immigration on the U.S. Economy and Labor Market: Report 1, 1989 Employer Sanctions and U.S. Labor Markets: First Report, 1991 GAO Immigration Reform Employer Sanctions and the Question of Discrimination March, 1990 U.S. Agriculture and Foreign Workers Effects of the Immigration Reform and Control Act - Characteristics and labor Market Behavior of the Legalized Population Five Years Following Legalization (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act papers by Briggs, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Conference: Immigration Reform and Agriculture, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Series XXIII. Immigration Coalition and New York Immigration Issues
  - Testimony on Temporary Alien Workers - Program Funding Inc., Immigration Coalition, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Pre-Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) bills, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) comments - Ruehle, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Coalition Resources Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) materials by coalition, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) news articles - Rochester, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Fowler and Freer Farms and border patrol, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - News articles for Cornell Cooperative Extension on immigration - Embrey, 1987-1994 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) - Coalition training, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) training - Embrey, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Immigration legal services center board, 1990-1993 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Legal service center formation, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Legal service center fundraiser (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Legal clinics - Corretore law offices, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Immigration legal services merger w/legal aid, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Immigration program of legal aid - Advisory board, 1994-2001 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Legal clinic - Legal aid, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Legal clinic - Cornell Migrant Program, 1994-2001 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Immigration National Day of Action - Batavia, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Immigration reform and perishable crop agriculture - Executive summary, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Immigration reform and perishable crop agriculture - Wayne County case study (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Commission on agricultural workers in Rochester, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Embrey testimony at Commission of Agricultural Workers hearing, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Commission of Agricultural Workers - Reports Commission of Agricultural Workers appendix, Commission of Agricultural Workers appendix II, 1989-1993 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Unskilled, Non Immigrant Workers - Embrey, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Fact sheets for employers - Embrey, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Alien Discrimation - Embrey class paper, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Farmworkers and Immigration Public Policy presentation - Embrey, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Agent survey - Immigration discrimination, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 28A)
  - Sodus presentation, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Annual training by Wally Ruehle, 1994-2002 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Migrant education conference immigration workshop, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Outreach memo - Florida, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Clearing house for immigration education (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Alert Immigration - Wally Ruehle (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Illegal immigration rights (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Local police and INS (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Taxes and immigrants (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - New York State assembly T.F. on New Americans, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Welfare reform - New York Plan, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Immigration, welfare reform and workshop notes, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Welfare reform presentations - Embrey, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Dream Act and New York College Bill (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Life Act - "V" Visas (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Students and English exam - Ymose St. Fleur in Albany (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - New York Immigration Coalition (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Citizenship Services Directory - New York Immigration Coalition (Box 24, Folder 46)
- Series XXIV. Alcohol and Substance Abuse
  - Alcohol Use Among Migrant Laborers - Morales, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Pre-Funding meeting - (FASAP), 1993 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Photos - (FASAP) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Proposal - (FASAP) (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Proposal year two, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Proposal year three, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - New York State funding proposal, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Learning from project (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Press and press conference (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Migrant Health Newsline article on FASAP, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - FASAP brochure (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Six month report, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - First annual report, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Treatment summary, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Summary sheets (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Final report, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Report numbers (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Work plans - Subcontractors (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Rural health outreach grantees meeting, 1994-1997 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Access to camps - letter to New York State Police, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Agency profiles - Diversity (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Police and farms (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Subcontracts - Year two and three (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - QSO agreements, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Carryover funds and budget changes (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Budget and program changes (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Community service boards (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Directors meetings and correspondence (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - FASAP supervisors (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Staff meetings (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Monthly reports - Staff examples (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Client case studies (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Cornell student project with Professor Rodriquez, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Employer information (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Staff orientation - Training notebook, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Staff trainings (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Community Develop Consult and Training - Peter Clark, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Group meeting flyers and schedule (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - FASAP presentation - by Alvin (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - DWI presentation (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Basketball/Football in Sodus, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Domestic violence and farmworker women (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Opening doors for FASAP, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Migrant agency training, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Diversity training for FASAP agencies, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - African Americans and Chemical Abuse Training - David Grant, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Rushville - Diversity training and consult, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - East Coast Health Forum, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Treatment providers meeting, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Diversity management training, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Opening Doors diversity training, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Mexican learning lab, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Opening Doors reunion, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Opening Doors for FASAP, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - CASAS region II meeting, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Oak Orchard (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - FLACRA (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Rushville (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Rural Opportunities Inc. (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Restart (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - OASAS (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Main Quest (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Oswego Services (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension Impact Statement (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Farmworker Substance Abuse Action Plan, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Proposal with National Center for Farmworkers Health, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Midwest Stream - A and SA treatment conference, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - HSS letter form conference participants (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Harvest House, North Carolina (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - NYSAASAP - workshop (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Paper award for excellence, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Research articles (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - Diversity information (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - Wayne County drug and alcohol agencies, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 74)
- Series XXV. Historical Papers and Cornell Traveling Museum Exhibit: "Coming Up on the Season"
  - Establishment of archives, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Olaf Larson (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - William Friedland (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Archives NEH Proposal - not funded, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - On the Season - Oneida County exhibit (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Louisa R Shortwell (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Make a Way Somehow - Geneva exhibit (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Goin' North RMSC exhibit (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Migrant Farmworkers in Upstate New York, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Farmworkers in Wayne County - Embrey (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Latino History in New York State- New York State Archives, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Kheel Center - Farmworker paper (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Fruit Industry in Wayne County 1823-1984 - Wayne Historical Society, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Oral histories collected by migrant education (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Story of Puerto Ricans in Newark New York - Kamalsky, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Oral history by Jane Spring, Niagara County, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - New York Folklore: Migrant Workers, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Portraits of Diversity - Reyes Family, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - More Than One Journey - C. Jackson, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Diary of a Farmworker, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Agricultural history newsletter - ERS, 1992-1992 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Smile in the Wind - King Ferry documentary, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Photography on migrant farmworkers (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Migrant farmworkers records survey, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - New York State Documentary Heritage proposal - funded, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Exhibit schedule, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Exhibit publicity (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Exhibit poster (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Exhibit resources flyer (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Exhibit - Family gallery guide (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Tompkins/DeWitt Museum events (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Hammond exhibit events (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Cornell exhibit teaching resource grades 2-5 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Cornell exhibit teaching resource grades 6-8 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Cornell exhibit teaching resource grades 9-12 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - New York State Department of Labor - Guide to Farm Work, 1980-1989 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Permission to use photos and text (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Teachers resources SED funding (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Exhibit case study planning (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - National migrant conference workshop, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Workshop on resources (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Resources correspondence (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry's exhibit curriculum (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - NEH proposal, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Exhibit scripts - Draft and final (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Grover's original script (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Artifact list (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Exhibit proofs and photos (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - New Jersey history - Grover article (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Agriculture in the Classroom: Worker related materials (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Steinbeck Center - California (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - People on the Farm - United State Department of Agriculture (USDA), 1981 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Colorado Migrant Project, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Michigan farmworker programs, 1968-1972 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Apple harvest, 1900 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Niagara County Apple Harvest, 1915 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Migrant farmworker in upstate New York, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Union activities and extension, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Series XXVI. Farm Labor Topics - New York and Other States
  - Child labor, 1997-2003 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Child labor in agriculture GAO, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Child labor in agriculture status reports and recommendations, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Helping kids do the job safely, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Migrant and seasonal hired adolescents farmworkers, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Collective bargaining for growers (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Crew leader/contractors (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Farm Labor Contracting in U. S. - Pollack, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Communicating with employees (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Employee applications - Farm (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Employee agreements, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Field sanitation (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Fruit harvesting and labor (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - INS and farmers (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Guest worker programs (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - H2A guest worker program (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - AEWR H2A's in New York (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Labor supply (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Contractor registration - Department of Labor, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Farm labor contractor systems in New York State - Department of Labor, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Labor contractors (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Employee handbooks (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Housing reports (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Housing/Camps - OSHA (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - California housing (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Indirect Farm Labor and Management Cost - Krause, United States Department of Agriculture (USDA), 1982 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Housing non-traditional (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Federal housing loans (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Job descriptions (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Job advancement (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - MSAWPA, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - New York State Department of Labor workers rights handbooks (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - New York State contractor registration (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - New York State Department of Labor enforcement, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - New York State Department of Labor Agricultural Employment Bulletin, 1999-2002 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - New York State Department of Labor correspondence (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - New York Labor Law - Department of Labor (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - MOU - United States Department of Labor, New York State Department of Labor and Department of Health, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Record keeping system, 1980-1989 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Recruitment of agriculture workers, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Recruitment services (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Slaughter house workers (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Social security (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Spanish language agriculture resources (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - United States Department of Labor - Wages (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Unemployment insurance (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Wages (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Federal laws affecting agriculture employers, 1989-2000 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Arizona - Border issues (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - California - Association of Labor Relations agencies - Labor law (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - California Agriculture Employment Forum (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - California Hired Hands in California's Farm Fields - Fuller Agriculture Labor Research Symposium - June 1991 Proceedings Mixtec Migrants In California Agriculture Stereotypes, Emotions, Behavior and Overall Attitudes Toward Hispanics by Anglos Mixtec Migrants Farmworkers in California Agriculture Laws Affecting Farm Employment in California (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - California agricultural labor (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - California Institute for Rural Studies (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - California Institute for Rural Studies - Semilla newsletter (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Florida (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Iowa (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Maine (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Michigan, 1995-2000 (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - Nebraska (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - North Carolina (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Pennsylvania (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - Vermont (Box 27, Folder 63)
  - Washington State (Box 27, Folder 64)
  - Gemplers Alert Labor Newsletter, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 65)
  - Gemplers Alert Labor Newsletter, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 66)
  - New York State Horticulture Society (Box 27, Folder 67)
  - National Council of Agricultural Employees Newsletter (Box 27, Folder 68)
  - Farm Bureau, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 69)
  - Farm Bureau (Box 27, Folder 70)
  - Farm Bureau lobbying (Box 27, Folder 71)
  - Farm Bureau and labor (Box 27, Folder 72)
  - New York Apple Association (Box 27, Folder 73)
  - Agricultural affiliates and Gary Fitch (Box 27, Folder 74)
  - Council of Agriculture Organizations (Box 27, Folder 75)
- Series XXVII. Health and Field Sanitation II
  - Food safety and workers proposal, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Food safety and workers project (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Food safety video (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Worker survey forms (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Survey raw results, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Survey project meeting and timelines, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Survey project correspondence, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Intern Journal - McKay (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Intern Journal - Konwinski (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Intern Journal - Bauer, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Intern Journal - Bixby, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Survey interns final reports, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Presentation on survey - Bihn (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Worker food safety posters (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Food safety coloring book (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Food safety resources (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Child health voucher program - Engman, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Grower Survey Frutas, Hortalizas y la Seguridad de los Alimentos: Salud e Higiene en el Campo (DVD) Frutas, Hortalizas y la Seguridad de los Alimentos: Salud e Higiene en el Campo (Video) Field Sanitation Resources Manual (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Oak Orchard - Health Care Needs and Economic Impact of Migrant Farmworkers, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - New York Child Abuse Study - Newsletter article, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Children and health (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Enumeration project, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Nutritional status of migrant children, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Food and diet of migrant farmworkers grant proposal - Parra (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Community food proposal - Parra, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Welfare reform and immigration access to health care, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Cultivating Health - Adolescent Farmworkers, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - MSFW health regulations objectives, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - NCFH and overview of farmworkers, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Farmworker health outreach needs assessment, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Research data base - Farmworker health, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Farmworkers and health insurance coverage (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - HIV/AIDS and New York State, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - HIV/AIDS and migrants, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Food stamps (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Health center guide for clients (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Migrant health resources catalog, On The Road to Healthy Living, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Binational farmworker health survey, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Migrant stream forums - Proceedings, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Migrant stream forums - Proceedings, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Migrant stream forums - Proceedings, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Migrant stream forums, 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - East coast forum - Includes organizing workshop, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - East coast forum - Food safety workshop, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Migrant stream forums - Proceedings, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - East coast forum, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Migrant Health Newsline, 1993-1995 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Migrant Health Newsline, 1996-1999 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Migrant Health Newsline, 2000-2002 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Migrant Health Newsline, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Reach Out Newsletter, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - MCN Streamline Newsletter, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Migrant h news articles (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Migrant and Immigration Health - Penn State Conference Statewide Strategies for Health Care for Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers (Box 28, Folder 54)
- Series XXVIII. Agricultural Work Force PWT and Immigrants in Rural Communities
  - Culture letter series, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - "Brown Bag": Community Development and Migrant Farmworkers - Clark, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Northeast Hispanic task force, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Northeast center proposal - Conference, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Diversity- A rural response - USDA special need project, 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Immigration In Rural Communities Policy Implications - S. Martin, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Resolving rural racial conflicts - USDA special needs project, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Farmworker Institute: Kellogg proposal, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Impact of immigration on agricultural communities proposal - Embrey, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Latinos in Westchester County, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Assembly public relations task force annual report, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Worker to farmer resources (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Workers to farmer proposal - Embrey (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Mexican dance - Sodus, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Multicultural Resource Center - Wayne Cornell Cooperative Extension, 2001-2004 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Immigration proposal: Planning meetings, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Immigration assimilation in rural communities proposal - not funded, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Integrating Needs of Immigrant Workers and Rural Communities proposal - FRA, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Immigration project - Extension proposal, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Immigration - Other funding proposals (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Integrating Needs of Immigrant Workers and Rural Communities - Project summary (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Focus groups planning, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Focus group at Court Harvest with photos, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Sodus residents focus group, 2002-11 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Downstate focus groups, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 25)